Yes, listen to the Word of God. Let the weak say "I am strong!".
Let the sick say "I am healed!" Let the poor say "I am blessed!"
Right now in the name of Jesus Christ, the Word of God will continue to command every spirit;
That spirit , that spirit, that spirit, that spirit that is not of God;
Their mission is to kill, to destroy and to steal.
I command them out in the name of Jesus Christ.
By the authority of the Lord Jesus, that spirit
of stealing, killing and destruction, out!
That spirit that hinders you...out!
Where can you go from His presence?
I'm talking to that familiar spirit, where can you go from His presence?
You familiar spirit, where can
you go from His presence?
You familiar spirit, where can you go from God's presence?
Manifestation of evil spirits
When you know these people, you will know that they hate power and might.
Just speak out!
Manifestation of evil spirits
Every hidden place you are
I command you out!
You evil spirit, every hidden place you hide,
Manifestation of evil spirits
Tell your neighbor, I am called by the name of Jesus.
I can't hear you!
Remain silent.
Leave the rest for the Holy Spirit
You continue to pray in your spirit
Manifestation of evil spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Let me see your hand.
The Scoan Sunday Mass Prayer
Say, "let the power of God locate me."
Locate me Lord.
Vomiting Blood and poisonous substances.
Locate me.
Manifestation of evil spirits
Say, "fix me oh Lord."
Fix me.
Say, "fix my spirit!"
Fix my spirt.
In the name of Jesus, fix my spirit.
Say fix my spirit.
Fix me oh Lord.
Fix my spirit.
Fix my heart.
Fix my soul, my mind, and conscience.
Fix them.
Fix my spirit.
In the name of Jesus.
In the name of Jesus
Open your lips, open your lips, open your lips.
Manifestation of evil spirits
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Do you know what it means to fix your spirit?
If the Lord fixes your spirit, He will fix your
spirit with the spirit of God.
Now you want Him to fix your spirit.
He will fix it with Himself and your join your spirit to Himself.
Our spirit is joined with God's Spirit
to declare that we are one.
It is when our spirit is joined to His Spirit
that we are declared as a true child of God.
Say, "fix my spirit o, Lord!"
Fix my spirit in the name of Jesus.
Fix my spirit.
Prayer
Manifestation of evil spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Viewers wherever you are, whatever medium you are using to watch us.
Those of you who are under the influence of this voice.
I declare that spirit not of God...wanted.
Vacate in the name of Jesus.
You evil spirit, vacate in the name of Jesus.
Their body is not your temple.
Right now begin to vacate.
Begin to quit in the name of Jesus.
I say quit.
Our body is the temple of God.
Our body is the temple of the Holy Ghost.
I say, any strange spirit that is not of Jesus, quit!
Quit
I command you wanted.
I command out!
I say out!
Out!
Let the will of God be done.
The will of God be done.
Every will that is not the will of God...out!
Let the will of God be done.
Every will that is not of God.
Every will that is not of Jesus.
Out!
Right now it is time for healing.
Every organ that is not functioning in your
system - begin to function.
Begin to function.
Say "Every organ that is not functioning in your
system, faculties...begin to function.
By the blood of Jesus and the power of the Holy Ghost
begin to function!
Begin to function.
Open your lips.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ
Listen, every organ, it could be your blood, kidney, liver...
just name them,every organ that is not functioning.
right now by the blood of Jesus and the power of the Holy Ghost begin to function!
Begin to function!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Viewers all over the world,
it is time to talk to you body.
It is time to talk to your soul.
It is time to talk to your spirit.
Listen, every organ that is not functioning,
in your system, faculties,
right now by the blood of Jesus,
and the power of the Holy Ghost....begin to function
Holy Ghost, begin to function.
Every organ in your system, begin to function.
Every organ in your system.
Every organ in your faculty, begin to function.
In the name of Jesus, begin to function
Begin to function in the name of Jesus
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
Right now..you fibroid... right now, I command you out, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever poison you might have taken in whatever way...in your dream...on the table of your enemy...
Begin to command them out.
Command them out
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Right now, I want to release this.
Listen, you are free in the name of Jesus!
This is the voice of God.
Say, "I am free in the name of Jesus."
Say, "every organ begin to function."
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
I can't hear you?
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Say, "every organ begin to function!"
I can't hear you?
By the authority in the name of Jesus!
By the power of the Holy Ghost.
Every organ begin to function.
Every faculty begin to function.
Command...command..command
Vomiting blood and poisonous substances.
Viewers all over the world, command every organ to function in the name of Jesus.
By the authority in the name of Jesus
Every organ begin to function, by the authority in the name of Jesus.
Every organ begin to function.
In the name of Jesus.
Begin to function.
In the name of Jesus
My kidney...begin to function.
My liver, begin to function.
My blood begin to function.
Begin to function.
In the name of Jesus Christ.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
Give glory to God almighty.
Right now, begin to remember those who are in a helpless situation/helpless state.
As we are talking now, there are some people on the sickbed, in coma.
They are watching.
They are hearing.
Right now, I want you to begin to pray...stretch your right hand
Let the finger of God touch them to revive their situation.
Revive their situation.
Every organ began to function.
Begin to function.
Are you on the sickbed?
Are you in a helpless situation?
Whatever situation you are in?
Are you in a coma? Are you on the sickbed?
Whatever state that you are in, Jesus knows better.
I command every organ to begin to function in the name of Jesus.
By the power of the Holy Ghost,
every organ begin to function!
In the name of Jesus!
Declare, it is well with my soul.
It is well with my spirit.
It is well with my body.
It is well with my career.
It is well with my home.
It is well.
Give thanks to God.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
Right now enter into covenant with your God, in the Spirit.
Here I am, so the rest is for you.
It is between you and God.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
Ask God and enter into a covenant with him.
He is a covenant keeping God.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
Viewers all over the world, enter into a covenant with your God.
God of Jacob.
God of Abraham.
Enter into a covenant with Him.
He is a covenant giving God.
Enter into covenant with Him.
Here I am!
Here I am Lord...yes!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
In Jesus Christ name.
Hallelujah.
I can shout Hallelujah now!
Yes!
Because you know the God that you are serving.
Say, I am not serving an unknown God.
Say, I know the God that I am serving, is a covenant keeping God.
God of Jacob.
God of Abraham...God of Isaac.
Hallelujah!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
Right now open our lips.
Pray for your nation...country
Jesus loves you.
Ask for God's intervention.
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B Joshua
God's intervention, open your lips and pray for your: country, nation, and continent.
God's intervention.
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Give thanks to Him.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
Ask God to make you a channel of love, where there is hatred.
Make me a channel of pardon;
where there is injury.
Make me channel of humility,
where there is pride.
Make me a channel of light where there is darkness.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass prayer
Make me a channel of obedience where there is disobedience.
Anywhere you go, you want to be a channel.
You want to represent God as a channel of
faithfullness, kindness, humility and love.
Open your lips and ask for the grace.
I submit.
I surrender.
Lord give me the grace to continue...in Jesus Christ name we pray
All things pass over, new things come in the name of Jesus Christ.
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Thank you Lord!
Glory be to God.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of Gods work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service and testimonies,
from the SCOAN...Emmanuel TV.
Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.